

Marco Hernandez Frontend Developer



- m www.linkedin.com/in/mhernandez-dev/

About me

Professional specialized in UI/UX, currently focused on creating beautiful websites.

With a solid foundation in Digital Design, I have a deep understanding on how to transform designs into functional code. To me, this is the perfect mix between creativity and logical thinking.

I believe in perseverance and smart work.

Experience

CRM Business Support at Microsoft (Vendor) (2022 - 2023)

In charge of creating the new Telephone Number Services portal.

- -Full rebranding of the portal
- -Full responsiveness
- -Updates for the business logic
- -Customizable components

Frontend Developer at Nomi - Payroll Services (2021 - 2022)

In charge of creating the website and updating payroll designs.

- -Full rebranding of the website
- -Full responsiveness
- -Multilanguage functionality
- -Image optimization

Digital Designer at El Debraye (2020)

Engaged in collaborative design tasks with diverse brands.

- -Photography and digital editing
- -Image optimization
- -Posts for social media
- -UI/UX web design

Education

Celaya University / Mexico (2014 - 2018) -Digital Design

Hallym University / South Korea (2018) -Media and Communications

Software









Bootstrap



Fiama



GitHub



PowerApps



JavaScript





jQuery

VSCode

Additional Skills

Photography and digital editing

Native spanish / Advanced english

